const questions = [
  {
    question: "How many sphere on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "4",
      c: "2",
      d: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "what the color of our sphere on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "Pink, Blue",
      b: "Green, Green, Blue",
      c: "Green, Green, Purple",
      d: "Blue, Blue, Grey, Red"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "How many cone on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "2",
      c: "1",
      d: "4"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Did you see another planet? if yes, what the planet is that?",
    answers: {
      a: "No",
      b: "Uranus",
      c: "Saturnus",
      d: "Jupiter"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "How many = small green tree on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "4",
      c: "2",
      d: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "How many sphere on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "4",
      c: "2",
      d: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "How many mushroom we have on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "4",
      c: "2",
      d: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question:
      "what the color of boxes around circle/sphere between our mushroom?",
    answers: {
      a: "Brown, Pink, Red",
      b: "Pink, Green, Grey",
      c: "Brown, Pink, Blue, and Yellow",
      d: "Brown, Pink, Blue, and Yellow, Purple"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "what kind of type Robot on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "Uyu",
      b: "BB",
      c: "HH",
      d: "Robotic"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "what the color sphere boxes beside the planet around us?",
    answers: {
      a: "All Grey",
      b: "All Blue",
      c: "Yellow, Pink, Green",
      d: "Brown, Pink, Blue, and Yellow"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "how many big tree we have on our planet?",
    answers: {
      a: "1",
      b: "6",
      c: "3",
      d: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  }
];

module.exports = questions;
